come2play.com 2017-12-17

# Privacy policy - Come2play

_**Come2Play Privacy Policy**_  
_Last Revised: March 23, 2014_

Come2Play Ltd. its subsidiaries and affiliates ( **“Come2Play”** , **“Company”** , **“we”** or **“us”** ) respect the privacy of the users of its online games available through our website at [http://www.come2play.com/Default.aspx] (the **“Site”** ) as well as through websites of third parties engaged with us (the **“Publisher Website”** or **“Publisher”** ), the Facebook platform and/or as installable mobile applications for iOS/Android/Kindle (the **“Services”** , as further defined in our TOS) ( **“User”** or **“you”** ) and is committed to protect the personal information that its Users share with it. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect and use when you use our Services. Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Service at [http://www.come2play.com/terms_of_service.asp] ( **“TOS”** ), into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference

  1. #### Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)

BY CONNECTING TO, USING, PARTICIPATING IN, ACCESSING AND/OR PLAYING OUR GAMES AND/OR INSTALLING OUR APPS ON YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, AND/OR BY CREATING AN ACCOUNT AND/OR BY ENTERING INTO, CONNECTING TO, USING OUR SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE “PRIVACY POLICY”), INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL THE APPS, DO NOT CONNECT TO, ACCESS OR USE ANY OF THE APPS, GAMES AND SITE, PROMPTLY ERASE ALL COME2PLAY APPS FROM YOUR MOBILE DEVICE AND PERSONAL COMPUTER AND DO NOT ENTER TO, CONNECT TO, ACCESS OR USE ANY OF OUR SERVICES

**Note that if you are playing our Games on one of our Publisher Websites, we recommend that you review the terms of use and privacy policy of such Publisher with whom you are interacting before doing so. Their privacy policy and terms of use, not ours, will apply to any of those interactions**

  2. #### Which information we may collect on our Users?

We may collect two types of data and information from our Users:

    1. The first type of information is non-identifiable and anonymous information ( **“Non-personal Information”** ). **We are not aware of the identity of the User from which we have collected the Non-personal Information**. Non-Personal Information is any unconcealed information which is available to us while Users are using the Services. Non-personal Information which is being gathered consists of technical information, which may contain, among other things, type of operating system, type of browser and keyboard language, computer configurations settings and any similar technical data, etc. In addition the Company collects behavioral information, which may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on the Services (which Game was played, when, with whom, Game results, amount of Virtual Items purchased and/or “earned”, time and length of Game play etc.), User’s ‘click-stream’ on the Services, etc.
    2. The second type of information is individually identifiable information ( **“Personal Information”** ). **This information may identify an individual or may be of a private and/or sensitive nature.**
    3. Users of the Services automatically provide their IP address mainly for enhancing the User’s experience and for geolocation (i.e., Country) and security purposes as further detailed below. If you play our Games on your mobile device, we collect your mobile device identifier.
    4. In addition, Personal Information which is being gathered consists of any personal details provided consciously and voluntarily by the User. The Personal Information is collected from the details the User provides when registering to the Site or to any Publisher Website, which may include, the User’s nick name, e-mail address, password and gender.
    5. Alternatively, Users can open an Account and signup to the Services via existing third party accounts (namely, Facebook account) used by the User ( **“Facebook Connect”** ). In the event that a User uses Facebook Connect, then Facebook provides us, per our request, with certain information about such User as is stored in such third-party account, namely, your Basic Information (nickname, full name, profile picture, gender, user ID, date of birth, list of friends and any other information the User made public) and game activity. Nevertheless, we DO NOT keep all of this information. We only store in our databases the following: profile picture, full name and e-mail address (to the extent that your e-mail address is set as ‘public”). All other User information provided via the third party website is promptly deleted.
    6. In the event that the User would like to send us Feedback regarding the Services, the User will be required to provide Come2Play with the User’s e-mail address.
    7. Please note: By playing a Game through the Facebook platform, you are authorizing Come2Play to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed that Facebook could provide to Come2Play through the Facebook Application Programming Interface ( **“API”** ) as well as you Facebook User ID.
    8. In the event that you use our Games via Facebook Connect or within the Facebook platform then you hereby grant Come2Play permission to post on your behalf on your personal Facebook Timeline. However, you may stop this at any time by changing your settings in your Facebook account.
    9. _Please note:_ By playing a Game through the Publisher Website, you are authorizing Come2Play to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed that such Publisher could provide to Come2Play in accordance with such Publisher privacy policy and terms of use, as well as your persistent identifier within such Publisher Website.

For avoidance of doubt, any Non-Personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists.

**We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Terms and the Privacy Policy**

  3. #### How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?

There are two main methods we use:

    1. **We collect information through your use of the Services.** In other words, when you are using the Services we are aware of it and may gather, collect and store the information relating to such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party service providers as detailed below.
    2. **We collect information which you provide us voluntarily.** For example, we collect Personal information which you voluntarily provide when you open an Account via the registration form or alternatively, using your existing third-party web account (namely, the User’s Facebook account). In addition we may gather information such as your e-mail address when you send us Feedback. We may gather, collect and store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below.
  4. #### What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?

Non-personal Information is collected in order to:

    * Enhance the Users experience on the Service.
    * Use it for statistical and research purposes and for customization and improvement of our Services.
    * Learn about the preferences of Users and general trends on the Service (e.g. understand which features are more popular than others).

Personal Information is collected in order to:

    * Offer advanced features to the Service.
    * Personalize your experience on the Service.
    * Reply to your online queries made through the Services.
    * Monitor and regulate Virtual Item transactions made within the Service.
    * Be able to contact Users for the purpose of providing them with technical assistance and support.
    * Provide the Users updates with personalized information regarding events, offers, information regarding the Company’s developments, new services, etc.
    * Determine general geolocation information (i.e., country) from which the User’s computer is connected to the Internet in order for us to know the general location the Users of our Services as well as in order to safeguard our Site.
  5. #### Sharing Information with Third Parties

Come2Play will not share any Personal Information it collects with any third party. Notwithstanding, Come2Play may share Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the TOS, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to User’s support requests; (e) respond to claims that any content available on the Service violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Come2Play, its Users, or the general public; (h) when Come2Play is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; (i) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through Come2Play’s authorized third parties service providers (including, as applicable, their affiliates as necessary to provide us with the requested services), as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j) cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing the User’s experience; (k) to let our partners and affiliates serve you with commercials; or (l) to embed the Service in any Publisher’s website for the purpose of enabling the provision of the Service within such Publishers Websites; (m) to enable payment through certain online payment method (see section 9 below); or (n) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure.

For avoidance of doubt, Come2Play may transfer and disclose Non-personal Information to third parties at its own discretion

  6. #### Deletion or Modification of Personal Information

If for any reason you wish to modify your Personal Information you may do so through the “Edit Details” tab within the Service. In the event that you want to delete your Account please send us an e-mail to: info@come2play.com and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws. In order to avoid any fraudulent behavior on behalf of the User we will retain your Personal Information for a period of one (1) year or as reasonably required

  7. #### Minors

To use our Services, you must be over the age of thirteen (13). Therefore, Come2Play does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using the Services

  8. #### Public Profile

For each User of our Site we create a personal segment within the Service which is accessible by other Users. The information which becomes public and accessible by other Users consists of your nickname, avatar, registration date to the Service, country, age, gender, publisher’s site, amount of Virtual Items within the Service, Games played on the Service, achievements and prizes, your friends on the Service and comments you have received and approved from other Users. In addition, you will have the option to insert any text you wish in the “what are you doing?” box. For each User of our Apps and Games (which are not played within the Site) we create a personal segment within the Service which is accessible by other Users. The information which becomes public and accessible by other Users consists of your registration date to the Service, gender, profile picture, amount of Virtual Items within the Service, Games played on the Service, ranking, wins and losses

  9. #### Payment for Virtual Items

A User may purchase Virtual Items on our Site by using certain online payment method (namely, Matomy Money, Facebook Game Payments, Google Play in-app purchases and iOS/OS X in-app purchases) ( **“Online Payment Services”** ). For more information please visit such Online Payment Services’ websites. Come2Play is not affiliated with the Online Payment Services, as each is an independent contractor, and neither is the agent or employee of the other, and neither is responsible in any way for the actions or performance (or lack thereof) of the other. The use of the Online Payment Services is at the User’s discretion and sole liability. It is the User’s responsibility to abide by all the terms specified by the Online Payment Services’ providers in their privacy policy, including but not limited to any age restrictions specified therein. We will collect the date payments made, items you have purchased, platform that the Virtual Items have been purchased on (e.g. Android through Google Play In-app Billing, Facebook through Facebook Facebook Payments, iOS through In-App Purchase on iOS and OS X, Web Application through Matomy Money), payment method for purchasing Virtual Items (e.g. Matomy Money) and all the information relating to transactions made between you and other Users on the Service. However, we will not have access to your Personal Information regarding the actual payment means. In other words, we will not know what is your credit card number or billing information etc. PLEASE NOTE THAT PURCHASES OF THIRD PARTY CREDITS OR CURRENCIES LIKE FACEBOOK CREDITS MAY ALSO BE SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL POLICIES

  10. #### Security

We take reasonable measures to maintain the security and integrity of our Services and User information and prevent unauthorized access to it or use thereof through generally accepted industry standard technologies and internal procedures. The Personal Information is hosted on the Amazon Cloud which provides advanced security features. Please note, however, that there are inherent risks in transmission of information over the Internet or other methods of electronic storage and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access or use will never occur

  11. #### Third Party Service and/or Software Providers

While using the Services we may be using third party software and/or service, in order to collect, store and/or process the information detailed herein. Such software includes without limitation, Google Analytics, which privacy policy is available at [http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html], Kontagent (Upsight) which privacy policy is available at: [http://www.upsight.com/pricing/privacy-policy/], Google Advertising, which privacy policy is available at [http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/privacy-policy.html], Amazon cloud services which privacy policy can be found at: [http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/] and Motomy Money, which privacy policy is available at: [http://www.matomy.com/assets/global-privacy-policy]

  12. #### Links to Third Party Websites

Certain links provided herein permit our Users to leave the Services and enter non-Come2Play sites or services. These linked sites and services are provided solely as a convenience to you. These linked sites and services are not under the control of Come2Play and it is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or services, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content advertising, products or other information on or available from such linked sites and services or any link contained in linked sites or service. Your access to, use of and reliance upon any such sites, services and content and your dealings with such third parties are at your sole risk and expense. Come2Play reserves the right to terminate any link at any time. You further acknowledge and agree that the Company shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused, by or in connection with use of or reliance on any services, content, products or other materials available on or through such linked sites or resource. Most of such linked sites and services provide legal documents, including terms of use and privacy policy, governing the use thereof. It is always advisable to read such documents carefully before using those sites and services, _inter alia_ , in order to know what kind of information they are collecting

  13. #### Cookies

When You access or use the Services, we may use industry-wide technologies such as HTTP cookies and/or Local Shared Objects (LSOs), commonly called Flash cookies, which stores certain information on your computer ( **“Local Storage”** ) and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your experience much more convenient and effortless. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. In order to erase or disable the Local Storage option in Flash you should use the settings option of Flash according to the specific instructions provided by the technology provider. However, if you block or erase cookies, or change the settings of Flash, your online experience may be limited. We also use certain third-party cookies. These are a different kind of cookies, stored on your computer by third parties, rather than by the Company (for example see Section 14 regarding Advertising). This kind of cookie is only read (and not altered by the Service) each time you visit the Service, and also when you visit certain websites or applications that uses similar cookies. Third-party cookies usually store only a Non-personal Information, such as the web pages you have visited, the duration of your browsing, etc

  14. #### Direct Marketing and Advertisements

**_Direct Marketing_ :** You hereby agree that we may use your contact details you provided us with for the purpose of informing you regarding additional products and services which may interest you, and to send to you other marketing material, transmitted to the e-mail address you have provided. You may withdraw your consent via sending a written notice to Come2Play by e-mail to the following address: [unsubscribe@come2play.com], or alternatively, responding to the e-mail transmitted to you and asking to be unsubscribed. In any event the instructions for removing yourself from the mailing list are available in the e-mail transmitted to you.

**_Advertisements_ :** We may accept advertisements from third party advertisers. These advertisers are carefully selected to provide information about products and services that we think may be of interest to our Users. Note that if you click on any of these advertisements, these advertisers may use cookies and other web-tracking technologies to collect non-personal and/or personal information about you. We recommend that you review the terms of use and privacy policy for any advertiser with which you are interacting before doing so. Their privacy policy, not ours, will apply to any of those interactions

  15. #### Push Notifications/Alerts

In the event that you use our Games via our Apps, Come2Play may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your device or by changing your settings within the App as is applicable to your device

  16. #### Changes to the Privacy Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Services and any information collected therein. Come2Play reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this policy on the homepage of the Site and/or we will send you an e-mail regarding such changes to the e-mail address that you may have provided us with. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Site or sent by e-mail, whichever is the earlier. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Services after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes

  17. #### Got any Questions?

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are most welcome to send us an e-mail to the following address: [info@come2play.com] and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe
